Artur Miłkowski

+48 694 895 300 art.milkowski@gmail.com github.com/improcode

I'm a specialist in React ecosystem. However, working with this framework isn't essential - I'm more interested in expanding my knowledge of concepts and patterns than being tied to specific tools. I'm currently learning how to write easily testable apps with clearly separated layers (communication, business logic, view). It is my belief that is the underrated element in the art of front-end development, especially in large apps.

Experience

Team Leader 9bits

06/2022 - 06/2024

Ecommerce platform internal; pre-production; maintenance

Responsibilities

- coding: 90% development / 10% maintenance
- team management (3-6 people)
- responsibility for delivering the sprint goal
- HR issues (evaluation and recruitment interviews, vacation approvals, etc.)
- decomposing business requirements into technical tasks
- increasing the competences of the team

Tech Stack Typescript, Next.js, NX, Redux-Toolkits, Styled-Components, Tailwind, Jest

Front-end Developer 9bits

05/2020 - 06/2022

Ecommerce B2B pre-production and maintenance

Responsibilities

- coding: 60% development / 40% maintenance
- · decomposition of business requirements into technical tasks
- buddy for junior developers
- coordination of developers' work (epic scope)
- production deploys

Tech Stack Typescript, React, Redux-Saga, Styled Components, Jest, Storybook

Junior Front-end Developer 9bits

07/2019 - 05/2020

Ecommerce B2C maintenance

Responsibilities

• coding: 30% development / 70% maintenance

Tech Stack React, Redux-Thunk, LESS, server side rendering (Express.js)

Front-end Developer Hatonero

02/2019 - 07/201

Administration panel for educational service pre-production and maintenance

Responsibilities

• coding: 80% development / 20% maintenance

Tech Stack VUE.JS, Firebase, Vuetify.

Real-time educational game/survey maintenance

Responsibilities

• coding: 100% maintenance

Tech Stack Backbone.js, Firebase.

Gap to learn programming freelance

02/2018 - 02/2019

Tech Stack HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Wordpress, Angular.

Account Manager Vena Art

11/2015 - 02/2018

Responsibilities

- customer service
- creative conceptual work
- project management
- preparation of offers for potential clients
- media production (print, video, web)

Tech Stack Microsoft Office, Google Analytics.

Education i

Certificate InfoShare Academy

06/2018

- 320 hours of workshop
- Topics: HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript, Bootstrap, GIT, SCRUM, REST, JSON, AJAX, React

Master of Economics Maria Curie-Skłodowska University (UMCS) Lublin

10/2015

Additional activity |

Forum Młodych Lewiatan

2012-2015

- Organization of business trainings and conferences (business education for students)
- Organization of Global Entrepreneurship Week in Lublin, editions 2012-2014
- Team leader

Languages |

Polish: Native language

English: Upper-Intermediate (B2)